<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog</id>
    <title>MEGA-Dawg68s Website Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-12-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog"/>
    <subtitle>MEGA-Dawg68s Website Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to bypass Admin Rights on a school computer]]></title>
        <id>https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker</id>
        <link href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to hack a school computer and gain administrator rights]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello! Today we shall be gaining administrator rights without
requiring any passwords from current admins. This took me years
to finally perfect and get working.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="quick-disclaimer">Quick Disclaimer<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#quick-disclaimer" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Quick Disclaimer" title="Direct link to Quick Disclaimer">​</a></h2>
<p>The way my school gives devices out is that my parents pay <strong>$1400</strong>
for a Microsoft Surface Go 2. You could buy a Go <strong>3</strong> for $800!
They also install all of the school rubbish on top of it. We don't
get administator rights as well. If you are in a situation like this
then, I support you hacking the computer, if you are given the device
for free, then I can't exactly put my support behind you, but I'm
not going to stop you. However, one major thing I want to say is
<em><strong>I DO NOT TAKE ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR ACTIONS</strong></em>
With that out of the way, lets begin!</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="prerequisites">Prerequisites<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#prerequisites" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Prerequisites" title="Direct link to Prerequisites">​</a></h2>
<ul>
<li>Another computer (With Admin Rights)</li>
<li>An usb stick</li>
<li>Your Bitlocker recovery key (Will explain later)</li>
<li>An unlocked BIOS/UEFI (Will explain later)</li>
<li>Sticky Keys is turned on (Press shift five times)</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="lets-start">Lets Start!<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#lets-start" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Lets Start!" title="Direct link to Lets Start!">​</a></h2>
<h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="if-your-own-computer-has-windows">If your own computer has Windows<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#if-your-own-computer-has-windows" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to If your own computer has Windows" title="Direct link to If your own computer has Windows">​</a></h3>
<p>To begin, we are going to need the usb and the other computer, launch
a web browser of your choice on the other computer and head to <a href="https://www.system-rescue.org/Download/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.system-rescue.org/Download/</a>
click on the blue text that says .iso at the end either Source Forge
or Fastly. When it has downloaded we need a tool to put the .iso file
on the usb. Head to <a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/rufus.ie">rufus.ie</a>, scroll down to downloads and click
on the first .exe you see <img loading="lazy" alt="rufus download" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/rufus-web-aaec6b37d1241f445b9ab3738181ffc0.png" width="1920" height="1080" class="img_ev3q">
once that is downloaded, insert the flash drive and open rufus, it should
look like this <img loading="lazy" alt="rufus open" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/rufus-open-246a87bef6fde40497893cbacadd15d5.png" width="473" height="538" class="img_ev3q">
click on the select button and find the .iso file we downloaded before
your rufus should look like this <img loading="lazy" alt="rufus open" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/rufus-full-9b973093443d20058420f5ce6cd081dc.png" width="562" height="752" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>If you get a pop up that says write in iso mode or dd mode, choose
iso mode. once that has finished, continue onto bitlocker!</p>
<h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="if-your-own-computer-has-mac-os">If your own computer has Mac OS<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#if-your-own-computer-has-mac-os" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to If your own computer has Mac OS" title="Direct link to If your own computer has Mac OS">​</a></h3>
<p>To begin, we are going to need the usb and the other computer, launch
a web browser of your choice on the other computer and head to <a href="https://www.system-rescue.org/Download/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.system-rescue.org/Download/</a>
click on the blue text that says .iso at the end either Source Forge
or Fastly. When it has downloaded we need a tool to put the .iso file
on the usb. Head to <a href="https://etcher.balena.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://etcher.balena.io/</a>,
<img loading="lazy" alt="Balena" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/Balena-web-31a8b1760012073743cf2f137e7f09de.png" width="1920" height="1080" class="img_ev3q">
and click download on Mac OS, go through the
set up, insert the flash drive and open Balena, it should look like
this <img loading="lazy" alt="Balena open" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/Balena-open-4f6b3ef15d1633ca739ee95eb17b87b8.jpg" width="2560" height="1600" class="img_ev3q">
click on the flash from file
button and find the .iso file we downloaded before, select target and
flash! once that has finished, continue onto bitlocker!</p>
<h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="if-your-own-computer-has-linux">If your own computer has Linux<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#if-your-own-computer-has-linux" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to If your own computer has Linux" title="Direct link to If your own computer has Linux">​</a></h3>
<p>You can follow the steps for Mac OS, except download the linux variant
Im sorry but I could get any photos, I am a linux guy as well but my
distro (Zorin OS) is broken.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="bitlocker">Bitlocker<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#bitlocker" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Bitlocker" title="Direct link to Bitlocker">​</a></h2>
<p>To tell if you have bitlocker, go to file explorer and press This PC
if you have a lock on the C: Drive, you have bitlocker and need to follow
these steps. If you do not have bitlocker, skip this step
If bitlocker is enabled on your school computer, we are going to need
to get your bitlocker recovery key, this is vital to gain administrative
privileges. So to get your bitlocker password, go to <a href="https://office.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">office.com</a>
and login with your school account and in the top right corner press
your profile picture
<img loading="lazy" alt="name and email censored" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/ms-account-75f671b06fd860ae41ab70cf8f58a1a5.png" width="313" height="241" class="img_ev3q"> now
press view account. In there click on devices. You should see a list of devices
<em><strong>IT IS VERY IMPORTANT THAT YOU SELECT THE CORRECT DEVICE HERE</strong></em>
To find the correct device go into settings on the school laptop, go to
about your PC, there should be the name of the device. For example,
<img loading="lazy" alt="Device name" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/name-of-device-150c8ea1d3f06fef12a8e45ab1bafb4c.png" width="484" height="362" class="img_ev3q">
Go back to the list of devices and select the <strong>Correct</strong> device
now press view bitlocker keys and press show recovery key,
<strong>Write this down, you will not be able to proceed without it</strong>.
If you see two operating system drives, write down both. Alright you can
proceed to the next section!</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="disabling-secure-boot">Disabling Secure Boot<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#disabling-secure-boot" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Disabling Secure Boot" title="Direct link to Disabling Secure Boot">​</a></h2>
<p>(If your device does not support secure boot you can skip this step)
To boot System Rescue, we are going to need to disable secure boot
this step varies between devices, I have knowledge on Surface devices
I will be using a microsoft surface for the example. You can look up on
the internet how to disable Secure Boot on XXXX (Your device type).
To begin, we are going to hold shift on the restart button in the start
menu. You will be greeted by a menu at has a few option like Continue,
Use a device and troubleshoot. We want to go into troubleshoot, then
Advanced options, now press UEFI Firmware Settings. You should be greeted
by a screen that says UEFI in it.
Go into Security, press on secure boot, now press disabled. Go to exit
and press restart now. Your computer will reboot and land on a screen
like this
<img loading="lazy" alt="Bitlocker Recovery" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/Bitlocker-recovery-b5044fd4bb66c88360a6c1288c47b3c9.jpg" width="4080" height="2296" class="img_ev3q">
enter in the key you copied down before, it should be correct and it should
continue and you should end up back in Windows, login</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="booting-system-rescue">Booting System Rescue<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#booting-system-rescue" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Booting System Rescue" title="Direct link to Booting System Rescue">​</a></h2>
<p>hold shift and press restart, you should end up back in that menu from
before, we want to press Use a device, you should see EFI USB Device,
select that, your computer should reboot and end up on a screen like
this <img loading="lazy" alt="System Rescue" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/sys-rescue-boot-f23642ead6d0b18b3d49b186ef21f0ac.jpg" width="4080" height="2296" class="img_ev3q"> select the first option.
<strong>DO NOT RESTART THE COMPUTER</strong> you will see a bunch of "Hacker Code", don't
worry, that is normal. You should end up on a screen like this
<img loading="lazy" alt="System Recue CLI" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/sys-rescue-cli-31ee4510d956b5f5bed878e2f2a6444d.jpg" width="4080" height="2296" class="img_ev3q">
We now want to type 'startx' (Without the quotes). you should end up seeing
a blue mouse in the middle of the screen. You have successfully booted
System Rescue
<strong>Tip: open this article in system rescue with firefox, you will need to connect to the internet</strong></p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="removing-bitlocker">Removing Bitlocker<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#removing-bitlocker" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Removing Bitlocker" title="Direct link to Removing Bitlocker">​</a></h2>
<p>If you did not have bitlocker, you may skip this step
Alright to start,
Open up a terminal window (the little $_ icon)
We now want to start a tool called dislocker. First we need to enter some
commands. We need to start with these commands <code>sudo mkdir -p /media/decrypt</code> and
<code>sudo mkdir -p /media/windows-mount</code> once you have entered those in we need to
get the partition info of the bitlocked drive. To do that, on the taskbar, you
should see a little hard drive, click on that. It should show something like this
<img loading="lazy" alt="GParted" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/gparted-90ab829c52b3bc1d3df9a79c02eec1b1.jpg" width="4080" height="2296" class="img_ev3q">
find where it says bitlocker and double click it, now where it says Path copy it
now go back to your terminal and enter this command
<code>sudo dislocker &lt;partition_name&gt; -p&lt;recovery_password&gt; -- /media/decrypt</code>
Change the partition name to your path (copy and paste. Copy is ctrl+c and paste is ctrl+shift+v)
You also what to change the <code>&lt;recovery_password&gt;</code> to your bitlocker recovery key.
<strong>There should be no space between your recovery key and the -p</strong>
for example
<img loading="lazy" alt="Example" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/dislocker-example-c3a867623e268fe6f844b806e3ddd669.jpg" width="4080" height="2296" class="img_ev3q">
(my colour will be different from yours)
click enter and if it works, there should be no errors. If there are, try again and
make sure the recovery key is correct.
We now want to run another command, this one will allow us to change files on our computer
<code>sudo mount -o loop /media/decrypt/dislocker-file /media/windows-mount</code>
Ff you have entered the command in correctly you should not get any errors
Congratulations you have successfully removed bitlocker! You move onto the next
section.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="setting-up-the-system-to-gain-administrator-rights">Setting up the system to gain administrator rights<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#setting-up-the-system-to-gain-administrator-rights" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Setting up the system to gain administrator rights" title="Direct link to Setting up the system to gain administrator rights">​</a></h2>
<p><em><strong>THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE TO PULL OUT NOW. IF YOU CONTINUE NOW AND YOU BREAK SOMETHING, YOU WILL HAVE TO EXPLAIN IT TO YOUR I.T DEPARTMENT</strong></em>
If you want to pull out, you can go to the X in the corner and press log out and restart. Do not forget to turn secure boot back on
If you want to continue, then lets keep going
press on the home folder on your desktop now press <code>windows-mount</code> on the side bar,
you should a bunch of folders like $RECYCLE.BIN You want to scroll down until you see a
folder called Windows, in there scroll down until you see a another folder named system32.
If you are in system32 you want to find a file called <code>cmd.exe</code> you want to <strong>copy</strong> that.
You want to open another file explorer (Don't close the current one, make sure you can
still see cmd.exe) and go to system32 again and now find another file named <code>sethc.exe</code>
you want to rename that to sethc2.exe, now go to the cmd.exe and rename that to sethc.exe,
now paste the cmd.exe you copied before. Now you should see cmd.exe appear. If have done this
correct, then you should now be ready for the next section!</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="gaining-admin-rights">Gaining Admin rights<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#gaining-admin-rights" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Gaining Admin rights" title="Direct link to Gaining Admin rights">​</a></h2>
<p>You are nearly done! If you have followed this far, it is safe to brag to your friends
that you are a master hacker. Lets begin the final steps! If you have completed last step
successfully, you should be on your lock screen, you now want to spam the shift button on
your keyboard, you should see a black box appear called sethc.exe. You have now bypassed
school admin rights! now, in the black box you want to type <code>compmgmt.msc</code> a window
should show up that looks like this <img loading="lazy" alt="Computer Management" src="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/assets/images/computer-mgmt-6fbba3a33f564578aef2249dde22a3cf.png" width="980" height="705" class="img_ev3q">
now go to local users and groups, then users,
<strong>This part depends on your school setup</strong>
now right click on administrators, click set password and set a password. Now press properties,
there should be a check box that says account is disabled, if that is checked then uncheck
it. If it is already unchecked then close the properties and right click and select change
password, change the password.
<em>If you get an error about password requirements while trying to enable the account, then close properties and right click and set password</em>,
depending on the password requirements, your password might have to be long. Once you have
finshed setting the password, close all of the windows opened and restart the computer.
Now on the lock screen, you should see an account called administrator, log into that.
If you don't see the account. go into other users and type for the username:
administrator (<strong>Must be spelled correctly</strong>) and whatever password you set
<strong>Now you are done!</strong></p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="what-can-you-do-now">What can you do now?<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#what-can-you-do-now" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to What can you do now?" title="Direct link to What can you do now?">​</a></h2>
<p>You can do whatever you like! You now control the computer. Somethings I recommend are to
set your school account to administrator in settings and users. Use that account instead as
using administrator might cause suspision as you login in front of teachers and snitches.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="congratulations">Congratulations!<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#congratulations" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Congratulations!" title="Direct link to Congratulations!">​</a></h2>
<p>You are now a hacker! You have bypassed the school I.T! Impressive achievement may I say!
Go brag to your friends, share them this article so they can do this as well, and maybe
the school will realise that installing school rubbish isn't a good idea.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="thanks-for-reading-my-blog-post">Thanks for reading my blog post<a href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/Hacker#thanks-for-reading-my-blog-post" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Thanks for reading my blog post" title="Direct link to Thanks for reading my blog post">​</a></h2>
<p>This took a long time to make, and you reading it justifies me making more hacking blog posts.
And with that, I bid you a farewell!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>MEGA-Dawg68</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/MEGA-Dawg68</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="Hacking" term="Hacking"/>
        <category label="Admin" term="Admin"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/welcome-docusaurus-v2</id>
        <link href="https://mega-dawg68.github.io/Website/blog/welcome-docusaurus-v2"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my first post on My website.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my website! It has been a bit of a hassle building this thing.
Docusaurus is an amazing static website builder, BUT the build steps aren't
very clear, for me that is a bummer, I have friends who like computers and
the realm of coding but they aren't very good with Javascript and HTML and
that means they won't be able to use Docusaurus. To be fair I am not the
best with this stuff either but I can read code and figure everything
out. Some of the issue was my fault, Just getting this blog post out was a
hassle as I was changing the default authors from the current Facebook ones
to me, yeah I couldn't do that without breaking everything. I probably just
need to learn how to use Docusaurus and I will be just fine. But still,
Docusaurus should really revise their getting started guide.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>MEGA-Dawg68</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/MEGA-Dawg68</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="hello" term="hello"/>
        <category label="general" term="general"/>
    </entry>
</feed>